Friends, hurry up!
The navigation shows it's still 14 minutes away.
Let's go home.
Where is it? Where?
In the crowd. Hey, hey!
Actually, I don't know which floor it is.
I'll go up with you.
Or should I bring a car?
Ahahaha!
Ah, don't panic, don't panic.
Ah.
Wow, I can't believe it.
I knew it was over.
You guys are so nice.
He brought me a partner.
I want to be a tour guide for three countries.
Okay, you do it.
I support you.
Let's do it together.
Divas Hit The Road S5·Silk Road  Memory from October 25th
Every Wednesday at 12 PM on Mango TV
Every Thursday at 10 PM on Hunan TV
Exclusive early access for members
More exciting content
Hello, Reba
Welcome to this season's
Fancy Flowers.
Please wear the local scarf yourself. Hello!
Hey, wait a minute.
How do I wear this?
Oh no, does it start from now on?
Are we in self-reading mode?
Open up the culture of Saudi Arabia.
What about your knowledge of Saudi Arabia?
No, I don't.
I only know that Teacher He is fluent in Arabic.
Hahaha, Arabic.
Maybe I don't have a deep understanding of it.
But it's fine.
Actually, this time joining Flowers and Youth
I wanted to explore places I've never been to
and take this opportunity to learn about them.
But, but, but...
I saw online that many schools in Saudi Arabia
are teaching Chinese.
I think it's pretty impressive.
So language shouldn't be a problem, right?
Everyone knows some Chinese to some extent.
I'm quite happy about it.
As for today's meeting...
Well, I'm definitely looking forward to it.
Yeah, because among the members, I've only met Qin Lan.
And that was during two previous events.
So, I'm excited to see everyone.
Gentle and soft.
I feel like the way of speaking should be
soft and gentle.
So I think it should be
a bit slower and more relaxed.
In terms of personality.
My personality is more impatient.
I'm more worried about myself
because I'm more impatient.
And my personality is
more extroverted.
I mean, that, that b-i thing.
Yeah, that m-d-t-i thing.
I belong to that category.
Right?
That's what I got.
But because of my work, I have to talk
so I end up talking a lot.
Haha.
So he should be the same type as me.
I remember, our personalities are quite similar.
I tend to get anxious, but I also have a tendency to procrastinate.
Every time I go out,
Clearly,
I might have already prepared everything for this matter.
But if you want to hurry up,
Your actions will become slower.
And then you'll start to forget things.
Especially when someone has to wait for me, I can't handle it.
I easily get anxious.
And when I'm anxious, I get angry at myself.
So now I've developed a habit
of trying to prepare everything the night before
for when I need to leave the hotel.
All the things I need to bring
are placed outside the hotel door.
I'm afraid that in these two days,
I'll lose my ID card or something.
Oh no, this, oh no, that.
I'm always afraid of these kinds of things happening.
Being impatient and having procrastination are contradictory.
But they coexist.
It's already 33, we should be ready to leave soon.
Let's go, let's go, the whole night bar friends, let's go.
The navigation shows there are still 14 minutes left.
I just said I don't want to be kept waiting.
But now, it seems like the situation is different.
There are still 10 minutes until 4 o'clock.
Oh, why does this headache keep happening?
Look, I've lost my target.
Oh my, this is really physically demanding.
This hand.
What's wrong?
Why are you looking at me like you've seen someone you know?
I bumped into someone I know.
Where? In the crowd, ah, ah.
Oh, I just don't know which floor.
Let's go up together.
Hello, hello, hi, sister, hello, you
Your hand is better now.
Haha, do you need tissue?
Thank you, thank you.
Haha.
I didn't expect our first meeting to be like this.
Hello, hello.
How did you all come here?
I rode my bicycle here.
And you, you don't look as disheveled as me.
Hehe.
Hehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehe
Hehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehe
Hehehehehehe.
Hehehehehehehehehehehe
Hehehehe.
Hehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehe
Hehehe.
Hehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehe
Up there, three people.
Come over here.
Hello, I want to ask if this is the smooth road VC.
Yes, hello.
Is this the three units?
Yes, thank you.
Who is this?
Who is this? Don't panic, don't panic.
Ah.
The meat is stuck at home, oh.
After this is installed, it's done.
Unit 173.
Number 462.
Really?
Catch up with me.
Or should I get a car?
Ahahaha.
Hello, hello.
Oh, sorry.
I'm very late, sorry.
Sorry, um.
Bridge North Road, Bus 10.
Oh my god.
Can I take off this clothes?
This is so annoying.
If I wear it like this, I'll ride a bike.
Ah, ah.
The last one arrived, right?
We're here, we're here.
Hey, how long have you known?
Take off your clothes.
Ah, you ran over here.
Ah, ah.
How did you come out from behind?
Then the top three will be awarded by the Counselor.
So there are no gifts.
Plants, right.
It's okay, no gifts, it's fine.
As long as there's no punishment.
The Counselor has prepared gifts for everyone individually.
Oh, that's great.
We still have something to gain.
New mission card.
I'm here, Flower Language Youth.
Remember.
Congratulations to Flower Shao for successfully completing the first class.
Departure is imminent.
I'm sure you're curious.
Who will be the first tour guide this season?
The first mysterious treasure chest.
Will be appearing at your doorstep soon.
Open it and you'll know if it's your tour guide.
Go back and take a look.
Can you stop riding a bike when you get home?
Hahaha, one hour each, hahaha.
Can we leave now?
Bye bye bye bye bye.
Hey, it's nice.
Hey.
Alright.
Let's continue working.
Help me with this overall shopping.
Here's one for you.
No difference.
Just as I imagined.
I think everyone should be like this.
It's quite lively.
And suddenly I think he's quite...
quite lively.
Because during dinner, someone said
that he should be someone quiet
who doesn't talk much.
But he's quite funny too.
I'm someone who doesn't judge by appearance.
I have a lot of internal pressure.
But I'm a very optimistic person.
Hahaha, you're so bad.
Without a car, you're making me...
Me and Kai rode our bikes here for 10 kilometers.
What's a card point?
You can use any form of transportation.
Public transportation.
Over an hour.
So you're 48 minutes late.
I've ridden it, you've ridden it.
If you didn't mention it, I would've...
Me and Kai almost died from riding.
I really enjoy eating with you, bro.
Hahaha.
I went too far, I admit it.
You did something and didn't say it.
I hope the tour guide will be...
because we have to go to Liade first.
It's a city.
I think a lot of things will be slightly more convenient.
Shouldn't we choose the smallest one?
Who's the smallest?
Hmm, not possible.
It might be difficult for him.
Because we just met.
We're still a bit unfamiliar.
We're slowly getting to know each other.
If we film the smallest one,
it might not be very considerate of the little kids.
So it can be someone in the middle.
Can it only be me?
Hahaha.
At least not me for the first stop.
How about assigning this task to Xidai?
Hahaha, please don't let me be the tour guide.
Xi Dao.
Haha, it can't be me as the tour guide.
Xidai.
Best wishes.
Take all the specialties.
Forgot your own bag.
Hahaha.
You have to find it yourself.
We can't help you.
Haha, let's go back again.
Here we go.
Why is our program like this?
We shouldn't mix things up.
Just like that.
Is it because we came back?
Hey.
The trip is not going well on the first day.
Hey, let's chat.
How do you feel about riding all the way here?
At first, it was quite exciting.
But then I realized I didn't have enough time.
Do you dare? Daring.
To make up for one minute.
I think I can fight for that one minute.
Suddenly, I had a realization about life.
The struggle in that one minute.
And winning it back.
The value of that one minute.
The feeling at that moment.
I was quite moved.
And then, along the way,
Actually,
I've been experiencing a sense of joy.
Because as an actor,
it's important to grasp the essence of life
and every bit of experience in life.
I've been thinking about that.
Actually, I haven't been thinking about the time
or anything.
Right.
Take the time away.
I want to take a look at my son.
My son always comes first in exams.
So I haven't let him down.
Open the Mango TV app.
Search for the Double 11 Exclusive Membership Benefits.
Then I'll start searching.
Ahahaha!
As expected.
Do you want to pretend to be a delivery box?
Is that so?
Hello.
Is this angle good?
Here are some of our small equipment.
These are prepared for us.
This is a power bank, right?
Ah, that's great.
Very thoughtful.
And a small umbrella, look.
Do you see it?
Yoyo, I'm your exclusive travel partner, Hualu.
Can you do me a favor?
Create a mini style outfit for me, the little traveler.
Little Hualu wants to look beautiful too
and go on the Silk Road with you.
So I need to put together an outfit.
That's great.
I love doing this.
Hahaha, thank you.
Thank you.
Today we are a rock deer.
Shake your eyes.
Singing too fast.
It's so wild.
Let's have a big drink.
A drink that we can never finish.
Turn on the recorder.
Turn on the record player.
Then the music starts.
If we sing more, you'll have to pay for copyright.
Hahaha.
Wow, haha.
I'm rock there.
How about taking pictures like this?
And during the trip,
encountering cultural exchanges,
let's have another folk song, another guitar.
It's so cool.
I want to take this bag with me.
Me.
I can't help but try this hairstyle with you.
This design you have now.
Will accompany you through the whole journey.
Through the whole journey.
Alright then, you can't bring a bag.
He doesn't want to, but he wants to.
Hahaha, okay.
No bag.
That's it, this is my rock day.
Rock flower day.
So handsome.
Hahaha.
So cute.
Let's walk the flower path together.
No problem.
But with my style of "no strangers allowed,"
Are you sure you like it?
Baby, my hands are a bit short.
My head is a bit big.
The bag won't fit.
Oh my, my face is a bit big.
I tried my best.
Oh, this one is good.
Come, let's walk the flower path together.
This is what I loved to do when I was young.
How about giving you a telescope?
Wearing sunglasses diagonally.
You'll feel very comfortable.
You recorded the impact.
These eyes are a bit small.
So happy.
This trip only has this combination, right?
Just the other things left.
Um, what?
Let's go eat.
Let's set off together.
We must wear glasses.
Because the sunlight outside will be very hot.
And wear contact lenses to protect our eyes.
We must wear them all.
Not one can be left behind.
Preparation is always good.
Otherwise, it will be troublesome when needed.
It feels like an adventurous mood.
Or else, when we come back, we'll be wearing glasses.
This person...
Hahaha.
Kind of like me most of the time.
Sleepy.
Alright, I'm really tired now, OK.
This definitely isn't me.
This one isn't me either. This one is definitely me.
Without glasses, I can't survive in this world.
A person.
Living without glasses.
Okay then.
Alright, that's simple.
Like me.
Just one suitcase and off we go.
Okay, this is me.
Thank you.
Ah.
I hope it starts a bit more smoothly
Ah
Wow, I'm amazed
I knew it
Where should we start?
It's over, this time it's really over
First of all
Let us give you some general information
OK, this is the overall competition
The overall spirit of being 13 years old
Now, the total amount given to you is 46,500 tickets
46,900 Sha Coins
The average is 837 Sha Coins per person
Monthly salary
837 Sha Coins per person
And then
This expense will be distributed to you after arriving in Lydia
The money for all the pre-booked parts
We will keep giving it to you
Okay
So I need to book all the hotels
Or do I just need to book Lydia?
Something's wrong
Just wait a moment
I'll take you there
In a natural style
Follow the tour guide
Put on some clothes
Let's go
Don't make me wait for you at the next stop
This hasn't even started yet
Do you want to resign?
I really want to resign
You know
Even if I collapse
But since I've been given this role
I should fulfill the role of an ambassador
Still need to be a good tour guide
Make everyone happy
Don't let any unexpected situations happen
Ensure everyone's safety
Steady and reliable
Let everyone have a happy time for these few days
Right?
You guys are really good
Even brought me a partner
It's good to have a partner
Exactly
This is comfortable
At home, right?
You're the tour guide, right?
I'm a member of the tour group
I've arrived at your house
I really am a tour group member
You really are a tour group member
Right, why are you coming to my house?
To meet another tour guide
I'm amazed by you
You didn't come find me
I came to find you
Don't mess around
Are you really a tour guide?
Yes, so come on
Wait for you, too
They don't let me reveal it
You know, right?
I'm suffering so much in my heart.
Brother, I'm already...
I'm already at my wit's end.
Come on, come up here quickly.
Here we go again.
I swear I'm about to lose it.
Is it okay?
Let's eat first.
After we eat, we can discuss.
So, to sum up,
Jinyaide will stay for two days.
Just two days.
Then we'll go to Ai'er'ao'la.
43 million will arrive.
3,028,700 million.
Let's go, let's go.
Let's get started.
Let's start with some fun.
Right, the nightlife here is very rich.
Don't oversleep.
Friend Liyade is a sleepless city.
It's worth partying all night for.
So, no more sleeping.
Kingdom Center Sky Bridge.
Do we have to eat Game Street?
If we eat this, we must eat Ai'er'ao'la.
High-speed zipline.
I'll play this.
You book the hotel first.
Let's book the hotel first.
How does it look?
I think it's good.
This bedroom has 9 beds.
This should work.
Yeah, let's go for this one.
Book it now.
So you've booked it now.
You've booked it, and then you'll come.
I'll search for Liyade car rental directly.
Look, there's a car rental guide for Saudi Arabia.
A sedan is about 140 Saudi riyals per day.
If you rent an SUV,
the price jumps straight to 800.
Ah, I'm really...
A sedan can probably fit 2 to 3 suitcases.
But it's definitely not enough.
We have to forcefully squeeze everything.
Wait a minute.
On the day of car rental, there's a 1,000 riyal deposit.
Three cars, 2,400 each.
On average, it's 2,400 plus 1,000.
I'm out of money.
Eating dirt at home.
Completely broke.
I'm broke.
This definitely won't work.
Yeah, this definitely won't work.
Yeah, I'm really...
Let's look for a car rental.
It's quite cheap.
328 RMB.
Oh, 800.
Just 1,000 short.
We're losing our minds.
Seriously.
You have to take it.
Can carry more luggage
Only two pieces of luggage for this
Four, two pieces
Three, three SUVs times three
That's nine pieces of luggage
There are seven of us
Nine pieces of luggage
Seems like it's not enough
How many pieces of luggage do you have?
You brought four with you
Hahaha, how many do you have? Three
Let's assume each person has four pieces of luggage
That's 28 pieces for ourselves
Leaving 25 pieces
Hahahaha
We're doomed, I'm telling you
Our tour guide career is over
Let's talk about it later
We'll rent first
No, we can't
Let's talk about it later
We'll rent first
There's a truck
Can we rent a truck?
Who knows how to drive a truck?
Can you drive a truck?
You can drive a truck
Oh, right
Oh no
Oh
I'm telling you
We'll never need to be tour guides in Croatia again
Absolutely not
Suddenly being a tour guide
Would be too much to handle
We still want to be
I really want to be
Continuously be
I have to win forever
I have to go from Croatia to Iceland
I want to be a tour guide in three countries
Great, you do it
I support you
Let's do it together
There's something easier than checking into a hotel
Oh you
I am your exclusive travel partner Hualu
Can you do me a favor?
Create a travel outfit with your style for me
Little Hualu also wants to travel in style
Let's go on the Silk Road together
Alright, let's dress up
Let's dress up
What does dressing up mean?
Dressing up means dressing normally
Dressing up is just normal dressing
Do I have to carry this with me all the time?
Or does it have to exist in a certain form?
It exists as a concept
in the form of a concept
Emphasizing a concept of companionship
Sometimes you can't see it
Sometimes it's too amazing when you can't see it
How about a hand guitar?
Cool, then I must bring my basketball
This guitar doesn't really suit me
I don't know how to play the guitar either
If you play the guitar, I'll carry it
You have so many things
They're all versatile
Universal all-in-one
Then I want teeth
Thank you, thank you.
Hmm.
Little deer.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Passport, driver's license.
Coming, coming.
Good girl.
There's no spicy food now, let's go.
Are you asleep?
I'm not asleep, not even a bit.
I talked to Xiao Wu on the phone yesterday.
It was already around midnight.
Finally counted the distance and everything.
Also found a lot of miscellaneous things.
A lot of small details that I didn't notice before.
Then let me show you my findings.
I really didn't sleep a single second.
How does my foundation look today?
Is it okay now?
Okay, let's just cut the hair, okay?
Alright, that's good.
Today is probably the first time I applied foundation on my own.
And I appeared in front of the camera.
So it seems like there are many firsts today.
It's really the first time doing my own makeup.
And being on a show.
You've been on the plane for so long.
And at least it's the first time being a tour guide.
Oh no, what should I do?
What time is it? It's 6:12.
Does this outfit look good when tucked in?
I'm not ignoring you.
I might have overestimated myself.
Wow.
It's getting difficult.
I've used up all the energy on this island.
Right?
Helpless.
Come on, I can do it.
Oh, I'm feeling good.
Oh, oh, oh.
Still closing my eyes.
Suddenly thought of me getting lost in Arabia.
Couldn't help but laugh out loud.
I don't know the prices on 6th Street.
I've already spent 14,000 on taxi.
Budgeted 6,500 for excess baggage.
Aurora activities cost 5,980.
So the cost of activities here
except for Aurora activities
doesn't require any money.
I hope nobody forgot their passport.
Did I forget something?
My mom said it's done.
Hello, Mom.
Oh, I've been a bit anxious about contacting Mom recently.
Don't worry, everything's fine.
Don't worry, nothing happened.
You're worried about nothing.
Right?
Exactly.
I feel at ease now.
That's it, hmm.
I thought I dropped something.
Turns out I left you behind.
Little Stinky, hahaha.
Yeah, Xiao Bai.
You used to take care of me.
My mom is a very gentle, delicate, and sensitive person.
When I'm with my mom,
I can't be too melodramatic.
Because I want to play the role of a grown-up
who can protect her.
Today, when we were recording,
you saw the hot topic, right?
I saw it.
Thank you, everyone.
Because you don't know me,
you made me trend.
Hahaha, it's really funny.
The funniest thing is that everyone said "Flowers and Youth."
I am that rain.
Hahaha.
Flowers and Youth,
I am that rain.
That's it.
What to wear at the airport.
The main focus is comfort.
Because I want to sleep on the plane.
I want to wear pajamas.
Hahaha, you can't tell it's pajamas.
I absolutely can't tell it's pajamas.
Even the pillow is...
pajamas.
Isn't it worn backward?
I'm up.
I wore my clothes backward.
What's the rush?
The main focus is comfort.
So I can sleep on the plane.
Hahaha.
My hair can be messed up, but not my hairstyle.
Hahaha, why do you bring special apples?
Let's do an unboxing video.
I used to envy others doing unboxing videos.
This is my small bag.
Inside, I have my passport, headphones, and other things.
And this cute little thing.
It's a lens that you can attach to your phone.
With it, you can take great photos.
Just clip it onto your phone.
This is just a random one I bought online.
It's one of those that you can hang on your phone.
It's quite cute.
I feel like this girl is very refined.
But actually, I'm not that interested.
in dressing up and being a dorm star.
But I didn't hear you in the sharing area.
I thought you were the mayor.
We thought it would be about 20-30 minutes.
A conversation in the car.
I'm going to the airport to meet my classmates.
We slept together last night.
For about 30-40 minutes.
So...
Your skin is also very sensitive now.
It's red here.
And here too.
I hope it gets better soon.
Alright.
Why haven't you posted in your sharing section yet?
I thought you were the mayor.
They are all mayors.
Yes.
Oh, I didn't hear it, hahaha.
When there is a special day or occasion
Encountering something
Yes, yes, yes
I remember many years ago, I filmed a dream
Then I returned to China
Now I am in Paris
And the driver
A driver took me to the terminal building
And then
He took me to the terminal building and left
I don't have his phone number
So I took the airport shuttle bus by myself
And transferred to another terminal
The driver
Do you know that I brought a lot of boxes with hamsters?
Two big boxes
And I ran after the airport
Now I'm empty
I believe they must be excited
Although there is a bit of uncertainty
Because there are many things beyond your control
But I still feel very excited
Because litchi is always ready for you
I just want to say something about this school
He said a word by himself
How to say, it means to believe that we can do it
Thanks to the exclusive social media platform Weibo
Follow Sina Entertainment Weibo and Weibo Variety
To learn more about the program
Search "Flowers and Youth" on Weibo
Participate in fancy surprises and interactions
Unlock more program surprises
Follow "Flowers and Youth" official Weibo
Join the program discussion
And the Fancy Team for a study trip
Thanks to the mobile cooperation
News media partner Hope
NetEase News, NetEase Entertainment
NetEase Talk Show, Deep Short Video Interactive Platform
Douyin News App
NetEase Eye
Cooperation platform
Fast Hand
Content cooperation platform Xiaohongshu
Cooperative partner Wanda Plaza
City commercial complex partner Wanda Plaza
City landmark
Naked-eye 3D big screen
Cooperative partner Changsha Xingguojun Naked-eye 3D Big Screen
Chengdu Lamborghini Center landmark big screen
Hangzhou Digital Binocular Naked-eye 3D Big Screen
Fashion Profit Factory Joy City
Special cooperation Baidu Cloud Disk
Universal key for coffins
Xunfei Input Method Video Monster Charging
Try to recruit and welcome live broadcasting
With the help of designated driver, Hunan Tianhong Voting Group